{
    "subject": "resource/Deadmau5",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/Ontario",
    "human_readable": "Deadmau5's hometown is Ontario.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9196525812149048,
            "question": "Is Deadmau5 originally from Ontario?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9195733070373535,
            "question": "What province or state is Deadmau5's hometown in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8971329927444458,
            "question": "Does Deadmau5 still live in Ontario?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7041778564453125,
            "question": "Where is Deadmau5 from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5498835444450378,
            "question": "Where did Deadmau5 grow up?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.290172278881073,
            "question": "What is Ontario known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.23669900000095367,
            "question": "What type of music is Deadmau5 known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1953270584344864,
            "question": "What other famous landmarks or attractions are located in Ontario?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1531408280134201,
            "question": "Is Ontario a popular place for musicians?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.12908755242824554,
            "question": "Can you name a famous person from Ontario?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Deadmau5's hometown is Ontario.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8000_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Ontario a popular place for musicians?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8000_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What other famous landmarks or attractions are located in Ontario?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8000_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of music is Deadmau5 known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8000_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8000_103.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8000_107.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8000_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8000_15.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8000_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8000_35.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8000_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8000_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8000_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8000_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents state that Deadmau5, whose real name is Joel Thomas Zimmerman, was born in Niagara Falls, Ontario. Therefore, it can be inferred that his hometown is Ontario."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}